hififun.net 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | HiFiFun.Net

We, at ‘ **HiFiFun.Net** ’, are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us.

"We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information."

##  **What is the meaning of 'Personal Information' here?**

“ **Personal Information** ” means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit  **HiFiFun.Net** ’s Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

##  **How we use Cookies?**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use Traffic Log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

##  **Your Agreement.**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the  **HiFiFun.Net**. By using our Web site and services, you consent to the collection and use of the information described in this Privacy Policy by  **HiFiFun.Net**. If we decide to alter or amend that policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

##  **Information Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

##  **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie –**  Google Adsense is our main Third Party Advertiser and

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on  **HiFiFun.Net** ,
  * -Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to  **HiFiFun.Net**  and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

##  **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We use the information we gather on the Web Site, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purposes of operating and improving the Web Site, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer.

If you have provided consent for us to do so, we may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from us or our affiliated companies or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered.

We may use your contact information or permit Selected Third Party to use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the Web Site or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be of you interest. We may also provide additional communications, promotions and information on new opportunities. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you.

**HiFiFun.Net**  cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Commitment. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. As a user of the Web Site, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Web Site, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Web Site.

##  **Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.  
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the  **Information Technology Act, 2000**  and Rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy.

##  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. The policy shall come to effect from the date of such update, change or modification.

For any inquiry contact us:[  **Click Here To See Our Email Address**](http://www.google.com/recaptcha/mailhide/d?k=01iGxMbwhVwu6vPrJFFm-QjQ==&c=BvEpdFAtpkp025kD1STz1AZsC5lej3PVe-ntigFgBRk=)  
**  
****_Thanks For Visiting!_**
